ANDRES BONILLA

Montreal, Canada 4383659614 Andres94b@gmail.com LinkedIn

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Current Programmer-Analyst AEC student and Mechatronics Engineer with four years of professional experience programming machinery for the industry. Looking for an internship in software development to apply my skills, learn from experienced developers, and advance my career. Solid knowledge of object-oriented Programming and MVC designs. Highly adaptable and detail-oriented problem solver with excellent communication skills in English and French.

RELEVANT SKILLS

- **Technical skills:** Web (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, ASP.NET), Database (SQL), Language (Java, C#, Python), Framework (Angular, React, Vue.js, Laravel), Software (Git, Node.js, Docker, JIRA, Linux, Power BI, Jupyter Notebook, Colab).
- **Personal skills**: Strong adaptability, Critical thinking, Troubleshooting, interpersonal relationships, Teamwork.
- Language skills: advanced English, fluent French, native Spanish.
- Interests: Web and Software Development, Full Stack and Back-End Programming, IoT, Robotics and Automation, Machine Learning and Data Science.

EDUCATION

AEC – Information Technology Programmer Analyst

LaSalle College

Sep 2023 – Present

Montreal, QC, Canada

Bachelor's degree in Mechatronics EngineeringUniversity Militar Nueva Granada

Jul 2011 – Nov 2017
Bogotá, Colombia

EXPERIENCE

Technical Service Engineer Imocom SAS

Mar 2017 – Mar 2021 Bogotá, Colombia

 Installation and programming of automation and robotics systems for injection molding machines in customers' production plants.

- Equipment maintenance in the packaging and plastics industry.
- Testing of machine systems and components to ensure proper operation and safety.

Experience Leader

June 2022 – May 2023

GrowPro Experience

Sydney, Australia

- Using Zoho CRM to keep customer records up to date.
- Improving educational and customer experiences by identifying opportunities and responding to requests professionally.

Server Assistant

Nov 2023 - Present

Restaurant L'Orignal

Montreal. QC, Canada

• Communication with kitchen staff and guests, taking into account dietary needs and preferences.